Nenad Lazić

Software Developer (Angular | C#.NET | Azure Cloud)

https://nenadlazic.netlify.app/ https://github.com/LazicNenad

Education

Email: lazicn378@gmail.com

Phone: +381 65 3683833

Pančevo, Serbia

<u>LinkedIn</u>

•ICT College of vocational studies

Department for Internet Technologies - Web Programming, software engineering

Belgrade, Serbia

October 2019 - Present

Experience

Quadro Consulting

Software Engineer Intern

Belgrade, Serbia

May 2022 - September 2022

- Successfully implemented CQRS Pattern with Clean Architecture with help of senior engineers and software architects
- Maintained and developed new feature on both front-end as well as back-end part of the system in Angular and .NET Web API
- Developed new SQL Database schema, views, stored procedures, user-defined functions in Microsoft SQL Server

Cycle d.o.o

Junior Software Developer

Belgrade, Serbia

September 2022 - Present

- Worked on implementing modular software architecture/design for the company's newest Minimal API Project.
- Utilized Dapper and Entity Framework Core as ORMs, wrote raw SQL queries, procedures, and triggers to optimize database performance
- Worked with Azure Storage Account, Blob storage, and Queues to enhance application scalability and performance
- Implemented authentication using Auth0 service
- Created whole application that uses Google maps API and Angular Google Maps from scratch
 that allows user to create Polygons on Map, update and delete them using stored procedure and
 save Polygons as Spatial Type in SQL Server
- Created whole application that uses Google maps API and Angular Google Maps from scratch
 that allows user to create Polygons on Map, update and delete them using stored procedure and
 save Polygons as Spatial Type in SQL Server

Languages

English - Upper Intermediate

Serbian - Native

German - Elementary

About Me

I'm a passionate and dedicated full stack developer with a solid background in Angular, .NET, Web API, Azure Cloud, and SQL Server database. With 3.5 years of intensive learning and hands-on experience in college, complemented by 1.5 years of professional experience in the industry.

Programming Skills

Front-end Skills

- Javascript
- Angular
- Angular Material
- HTML
- · CSS
- Bootstrap

Back-end Skills

- C#.NET
- ASP.NET Web API
- Entity Framework
- SQL Server
- Dapper ORM
- PHP
- Laravel

Other skills

- Microsoft Azure
- Design Patterns
- Software Architecture
- · Agile and Scrum
- Google Maps API
- · Git, Azure DevOps